ALAN SAPUTRA LENGKOAN

<u>alanlengkoan.com</u> | <u>alanlengkoan15@gmail.com</u> | +6285242907595

PROFIL

Hi.. I'm Alan, I Have 3 years experience in Web Development, Back Enginer is the position I'm in most often, PHP and JavaScript are the Programming Language I use most often. There are few Frameworks that I mostly used namely CodeIgniter, Symfony and Laravel. I'm currently studying nodejs and expressjs. I am also interested in the Dart Programming Language with the Flutter Framework in Mobile App Development.

EDUCATION

STMIK Handayani Makassar, Indonesia
Informatics Enginering Aug 2015 – Dec 2019
(GPA 3.59 out of 4.00)

EXPERIENCE

PT. Kumala Group Web Developer Makassar, Indonesia Feb. 2020 – Present

Create and Develop several modules that already exist in the After Sales. The module that I created is in the Tax and Spare Parts Management section. From the special technology side of the programming language using PHP accompanied by a framework that there is CodeIgniter because we work as a team, we use Git as Version Control System. The text editor that we use is Visual Studio Code.

PT. Upana Pelopor Aplikasi Adikarya

Makassar, Indonesia

Back End Web Developer Intern

May 2019 – Jul. 2019

Combine the results of the Front End display that has been approved by the client, to the programming language that I use in working on the website, is PHP with PHP CodeIgniter Framework as for the Package I use is Composer because we work as a team using Git as Version Control System, for Text Editor what I use is Visual Studio Code.

Dapurtani Makassar, Indonesia

Chief Technology Officer

Apr. 2018 – Jul. 2019

Build a special kitchen company engaged in the sale of vegetables, fruit Organic, and Hydroponic from local farmers and make our shop platform for bringing together consumers and producers.

Self EmployedMakassar, IndonesiaWeb DeveloperFeb 2018 – Present

VOLUNTEER EXPERIENCE

PERDAMI (Indonesian Ophtalmologists' Association)	Makassar, Indonesia
Volunteer IT	Sept. 2019 – Sept. 2019

SKILLS

Language: PHP, JavaScript, Python, Dart

Frameworks: CodeIgniter, Symfony, Laravel, Express, Django, Flutter

Other: Mysql, SQL Server, PostgreSQL, HTML, CSS, Bootstrap, Materialize, Foundation,

JQuery, Ajax, Rest API, Git.